{
    "subject": "resource/Maria_Letizia_Bonaparte,_Duchess_of_Aosta",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Maria Letizia Bonaparte, Duchess of Aosta is Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9809826016426086,
            "question": "What is the full name of Maria Letizia Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9643576741218567,
            "question": "What is another name for Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9606202840805054,
            "question": "What is the last name of Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9565969109535217,
            "question": "Which name comes last in Maria Letizia Bonaparte's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9310702681541443,
            "question": "What title did Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9272964000701904,
            "question": "Give the full name of the Duchess of Aosta."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8826637864112854,
            "question": "How many names does Maria Letizia Bonaparte have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.882611870765686,
            "question": "Does Maria Letizia Bonaparte have a title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.851889431476593,
            "question": "List the first three names of Maria Letizia Bonaparte."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7636509537696838,
            "question": "What was the birth name of the Duchess of Aosta?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Maria Letizia Bonaparte, Duchess of Aosta is Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte.",
            "html": "dbpedia_971_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=List the first three names of Maria Letizia Bonaparte.",
            "html": "dbpedia_971_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Maria Letizia Bonaparte have a title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_971_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many names does Maria Letizia Bonaparte have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_971_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_971_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to the full name \"Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde\" as Maria Letizia Bonaparte, which confirms that her full name is indeed Marie Laetitia Eug\u00e9nie Catherine Ad\u00e9la\u00efde Bonaparte."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}